https://hihostels.ca/en/privacy-policy

HI Regina
HI Rivière-du-Loup, Auberge internationale de Rivière-du-Loup
HI Québec, Auberge internationale de Québec
HI Rivière-du-Loup, Auberge internationale de Rivière-du-Loup
HI Québec, Auberge internationale de Québec
HI Rivière-du-Loup, Auberge internationale de Rivière-du-Loup
HI Québec, Auberge internationale de Québec
HI Rivière-du-Loup, Auberge internationale de Rivière-du-Loup
HI Québec, Auberge internationale de Québec
HI Rivière-du-Loup, Auberge internationale de Rivière-du-Loup
Our Privacy Policy
Hostelling International Canada respects the personal privacy of our customers and we take the responsibility of ensuring the security of your personal information very seriously.
If we ask you to provide us with any personal information, we will tell you the purposes for which we intend to use that information. We will not collect, use or disclose your personal information without your consent. We will never sell any information obtained from you to a third party.
Information Collection, Use & Disclosure
By becoming a member of HI Canada, you must provide certain personal information which is added to our internal membership database. The information contained in the database can only be used for purposes related to Hostelling International.
When you purchase your Hostelling International membership, we must request information needed to complete the processing of your order and billing.Contact details and membership purchase information is also collected for the purpose of replacing lost, stolen or damaged membership cards. We may also use the information collected to send you AGM and election material, member magazines, newsletters, email notices, research and surveys and other correspondence. We will only send this type of information to you with your consent.We will use information on site traffic and member demographics to compile statistics and reports for Hostelling International's use. We analyze aggregated information to understand our customers and their needs. The information used for this purpose does not include personally identifiable data.Website Security
HI Canada will use the appropriate security safeguards to protect your personal information against loss, theft and unauthorized access. Any personal information you provide to Hostelling International is 128-bit encrypted and delivered over a secure server. Access to personal information is restricted to authorized HI Canada personnel only.
Cookies
A "cookie" is a small file that is stored on your computer's hard drive. The browser stores the message in a text file and the message is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server.
HI Canada makes limited use of cookies on our website so that we can provide you with faster service, consistent and updated information and an overall better web experience. We do not use cookies to track personally-identifiable information or your movements after leaving our website.
Most browsers allow you to turn off cookies, and the help menu of your browser should tell you how to do so. However, doing this will hinder our website's performance and negatively impact your experience on our site.
Annual General Meetings  All regions of HI Canada hold an annual general meeting (AGM . AGMs provide an excellent opportunity for HI members to learn about the Association's achievements in the past year, meet the Board of Directors that represent membership interests, hear election results as well as discuss and vote on Special Resolutions regarding management and strategic issues.
As part of your membership, you will receive a notice about the AGM at least once a year. Participation and attendance at the AGM is completely voluntary and is an opportunity for you to lend your voice to the Association.
Member Magazine HI Canada produces a digital magazine several times a year.  This magazine is designed to keep you up-to-date on HI news and member events as well as share travel-related stories and tips from here at home and around the world. This digital magazine is free and sent only to members who have chosen to receive it.
Email Newsletters  HI Canada collects your email address so that we can send you an electronic newsletter. The electronic newsletters contain membership / HI hostel updates, travel tips and other budget travel-related information. Newsletters are only sent to people who have chosen to receive them.  Each newsletter you receive includes simple instructions on how to unsubscribe from our mailing list at any time.
Research & Surveys  From time to time, we may conduct research or surveys that request demographic information (such as age range and gender) and travel preferences. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary. The information collected will only be shared with third parties in aggregate form; no individual personal information will ever be given to third parties unless we have your express permission or you have been notified.
Accuracy and Access  HI Canada strives to ensure that any personal information we collect is accurate and complete for the purposes with which we will use it. At your request, we will provide you with a statement of the personal information we have collected about you. If our records regarding your personal information are inaccurate or incomplete, we will amend the information at your request immediately.
For more information  The above statement discloses the privacy practices and policies for HI Canada's website. If you have any questions about these practices and policies or would like to file a complaint, please contact HI Canada's Privacy Officer at privacy.officer@hihostels.ca.
Close
Subscribe
Stay connected by receiving the latest news for HI Canada right in your mailbox.
What's up this winter?
Some of our hostels have hunkered down into a temporary hibernation for the fall or winter. Find out what's open and when others are reopening.
Read more
(Close window)
Share
Top
